htbridge.ch 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy | ImmuniWeb

### 1\. Introduction

[www.immuniweb.com](https://www.immuniweb.com/), hereinafter “this website”, is owned and operated by High-Tech Bridge SA, a Swiss company registered in Swiss Federal Commercial Register under No. [CH-660.3.042.007-9](http://ge.ch/hrcintapp/externalCompanyReport.action?companyOfrcId13=CH-660-3042007-9&ofrcLanguage=2) (hereinafter "High-Tech Bridge"), domiciled at 29 Route de Pre-Bois, World Trade Center II, CH-1215 Geneva, Switzerland.

High-Tech Bridge is committed to protect privacy and security of your personal information that we may collect and process with your consent when you use this website.

### 2\. Scope

This Policy applies to all users who visit, or otherwise uses, this website and all the functionality it provides. Please read this Policy carefully before using the website or submitting any personal information to it.

You are encouraged to review this Policy whenever you visit this website to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide is used.

By using this website, you agree to and accept this Privacy Policy without any reservation.

### 3\. Collection, Storage and Removal of Information

In order to analyze website visitor's behavior and to provide a better service, High-Tech Bridge may record standard technical information about the website visitors, such as their IP address, browser and operating system versions, and the referring websites.

High-Tech Bridge collects Personally Identifiable Information (PII) (e.g. names, titles, postal addresses, email addresses, etc.) only when voluntarily submitted by you via existing functionality of this website for a specific purpose (e.g. trial request). High-Tech Bridge may also collect the information, including PII, voluntarily submitted by you via alternative or non-digital means (e.g. email, fax, postal service, etc.) for a specific purpose (e.g. sales inquiry, job application, etc.).

The information you provide is used only to fulfill your specific request(s) unless you give a prior explicit permission to use it in another manner.

High-Tech Bridge securely stores and processes the information submitted as long as reasonably required to pursue the initial purpose of the information submission.

The information can be deleted if requested to do so in writing or via an automated functionality (e.g. unsubscribe link will remove your subscription and the related PII).

Once deleted, the information cannot be recovered and any claims for interrupted or undelivered service because of the information removal will be null and void.

Please contact us at [removals@htbridge.com]() with “My PII Data Removal” in the subject for any information deletion requests. Emails with different subject will be undelivered.

### 4\. Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

High-Tech Bridge will never voluntarily disclose your personal information to any unauthorized third party unless:

(a) High-Tech Bridge is required to do so by Swiss law or other applicable law; or

(b) High-Tech Bridge is trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud; or

(c) High-Tech Bridge is investigating fraud that has already taken place.

We will make our best reasonable effort to inform you that your data was requested whenever we are legally permitted to do so.

### 5\. Cookies

This website may use cookies and other tracking technologies to provide a better user experience and provide information publicly available on our website to you in the most convenient form and format.

Personally Identifiable Information is not collected via our cookies and other tracking technologies, however, if you previously provided the personally identifiable information, the cookies may be tied to such information.

### 6\. Commitment to Information Security

We undertake our best reasonable effort to keep your personal information secure. Only the authorized employees of High-Tech Bridge have access to this information.

High-Tech Bridge is an ISO 27001 certified company that adheres to various security and privacy procedures of this security standard. High-Tech Bridge's employees also adhere to internal information security policies and procedures to safeguard your personal information.

### 7\. Inquiries

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about this Policy, please contact High-Tech Bridge by e-mail: [info@htbridge.com]()

### 8\. Changes

High-Tech Bridge reserves the right to make reasonable and good faith changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice.

Any changes will be posted online without delay. Any substantial changes, or changes that may considerably impact your privacy or security, will be promptly communicated to you by email or any other available mean of communication.

The changes will only apply on a going forward not retroactive basis.

_Version 1.4  
May 29, 2018_
